All right, so now
let's look at how
to get feedback on
an intro or how
to use AI to
write them for you.
So for the AI,
you can give it
your video's title and
then you can give
it the top three
questions you think your
viewers will have. And
you can ask it
to write an intro
and it will do
one that you must
then edit to sound
like you. If you
don't give it those
top three expectations, just
the title, it's going
to make them up
for itself. And it's
going to tell you
what it thinks they
are. Just always check
that they seem on
track. That's one way.
Otherwise, you can write
your own intro and
then you can ask
it for feedback in
the intro bot. And
I use this for
my own content. It's
very good. Just whatever
you do, don't not
use it. Then for
getting AI feedback on
scripts, what you want
to do is go
to point bot. This
is not a bot
that writes your script.
It's a bot that
gives you feedback that
might suggest an optimized
version. So here's how
I'd recommend using it.
Just cut out one
point of your script,
paste it in and
ask for feedback. It's
going to help spot
early payoff, complexity and
any areas of confusion.
Now, the thing you
need to understand is
if I write an
awful script, it's not
going to give a
great one back. It's
slightly worse script. So
you still need to
put the effort in
and the better the
script you give it,
the better it will
make it. Now, the
next option is pretty
cool. Paste your whole
script in and just
ask it, why did
this script flop? Even
if you haven't posted
it, just try it.
It's going to give
you ten potential fixes.
Again, use your brain
here. Some of these
fixes might instantly make
you go, oh, yeah,
duh. Others might make
you go, I'm not
sure it's that big
a deal. If you're
going to make any
changes based on it,
just make the changes
that feel the most
obvious to you. And
that's it. These these
bots are amazing at
leveling you up. So
please, please do use
them. All right. Now,
if you remember, let's
look at how you
submit intros for human
feedback in the chat.
Here's how to do
it without wasting our
time. So put your
intro on a Google
Doc like this. Make
the doc open access
like this, meaning we
can then tag comments
on it. I'm going
to say that again.
Put the intro on
a doc like this,
then make the doc
open access like this,
meaning we can tag
comments. If you forget
to make it open
access when you share
that document with us,
we can't tag these
comments on it. And
that's the best way
for us to give
feedback. Then the same
is true if you
want us to check
out like one section
of a script. Now,
you've got to make
sure that you're not
going to be able
to see the comments
on the screen. You've
been told we don't
do full script feedback
as part of this
service. If you want
that, you can hire
one of the team
externally to do it.
But we can look
at a section and
it's the same thing.
Get the script in
the document, make it
open access and then
make it clear where
in the script you
want us to look.
Ideally, you can just
highlight a section red
or a color. And
that's it. And look,
if at any time
you're like, I'm not
sure if I'm doing
this right. Just ask.
We honestly don't care
if you put it
in the wrong room.
We'll just tell you
where to put it
next time. Like I've
had people say I
didn't use the feedback
because I was so
scared I was going
to get it wrong.
Why? I'm not a
monster. Do I look
like a monster? I'm
a nice guy.